businessvibes.com 2010-09-11

# Privacy | BusinessVibes - Connecting Businesses

| **Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
Data Protection   
Registration Data   
Your Profile and Contact Management   
Visibility of your Profile to Non-Members of BusinessVibes   
Search Functions   
Changes to this Privacy Policy   
**Data Protection**  
  
BusinessVibes recognizes that any data provided by the User to BusinessVibes is extremely important to the User, and BusinessVibes shall therefore be particularly sensitive in handling such data. In particular, BusinessVibes shall not provide any personal data of the User to any third party. BusinessVibes shall also make this privacy notice available anywhere where personal data may be required. 

BusinessVibes shall use user’s Personal Data solely to provide them the BusinessVibes Services on the Internet for which they have registered. BusinessVibes will never pass their Personal Data on to any third party, neither for advertising, nor for marketing for any other purposes. 

With the exception of some general information about user’s profession, users alone decide which of the Personal Data they have made available to BusinessVibes may be displayed by BusinessVibes to other members of BusinessVibes. Persons not registered with BusinessVibes may only view Personal Data to the extent that the user enables and allow them to do so. 

Top  
**Registration Data**  
  
In the process of opening a BusinessVibes account, BusinessVibes needs to collect and process certain elements of Personal Data in the course of the registration process. First of all, this consists of the following data: 

First name, surname, address   
Business email account   
Business telephone/fax number   
Birth date  
Professional status   
Company name  
Job Title   
Industry   
Country, state and city of your company 

The following Personal Data from these mandatory fields is accessible to other BusinessVibes Members without any restrictions: 

Job Title   
Company name   
Country, state and city of your company   
Company name

BusinessVibes does not display your name or email address to other members unless you expressly grant permission on an individual basis.   
  
Top  
**Your Profile and Contact Management**  
  
The following items of the Personal Data provided by users on BusinessVibes are visible to all other BusinessVibes Members: 

Professional status   
Company name  
Job Title   
Industry   
Country, state and city of your company 

All other BusinessVibes Members may access your Profile and view the information displayed on the Profile.   
  
Many emails you initiate through BusinessVibes, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your name in the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network and your company. BusinessVibes merely provides the User with a platform to establish contact with other users, and only provides those technical applications that allow users to contact one another. Regarding content, BusinessVibes does not take part in any communication between users. The users alone are responsible for all communication in the network. BusinessVibes shall not be held liable if users are unable to contact one another over BusinessVibes website. Furthermore, BusinessVibes shall not be liable for breaches of duty in relation to agreements entered into between users.   
  
Top  
  
**Visibility of your Profile to Non-Members of BusinessVibes**  
  
When you register, your default privacy settings aim to promote the spirit of networking. The data contained in your company profile is visible to non-members of BusinessVibes and could be traceable by search engines on the Internet. This, however, does not include personal contact details such as user-specific email addresses or phone numbers. The main contact numbers for your company will be visible, and you may also modify the level of your privacy at any time. This means that you decide whether to increase your level of privacy or opt in favor of more visibility online, enabling more exposure of your profile for potential business partners.   
  
Top  
  
**Search Functions**  
  
The BusinessVibes Services offer various possibilities to search for BusinessVibes Members. These search functions may assist you, for example, in finding other BusinessVibes Members with similar interests. The search functions can also help you to initiate contact with other BusinessVibes Members who offer exactly what you are looking for. Thus, you can find the contacts you need - and systematically expand your personal network   
  
Top  
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
  
BusinessVibes may update this privacy policy. In the event if there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.   

---  
Copyright© Infiniti Research Ltd. 2010
